I'm the one who called it in
Cynthia knows nothing about it
Whatever anger you have
take it out on me
I didn't come here to argue today
Withdraw the report right now
Get Daniel out
No way
You
If you don't get Daniel out
I'll shout here with a megaphone every day
Tell everyone how you mistreat your in-laws
I'll ruin your business
Let's see who dares to buy your forest frogs
If you dare to do that
I'll call the police
Your whole family stole trade secrets
That's a much more serious crime
than what Daniel is facing now
When the time comes
you two will end up in jail as well
Cynthia, never mind that he's heartless
Daniel is your own brother
You're just going to watch him go to jail
He should pay for his mistakes
Besides
when he did those things
he never treated me like a sister
You ungrateful brat
You heartless thing
Go ahead and scream. All my life
whenever Daniel got in trouble
I was the one who got blamed
I'm used to it
If you don't leave
I really will call the police
and send your whole family to jail for a reunion
You just wait